So, I graduated from college in 1986
from the University of Georgia, and if
you do the quick math, that makes me 55
YEARS OLD.
AND I love being over 50. There's
something magical about it, particularly
as a woman, about being over 50 is I
just don't care what people think
anymore, and it's very freeing.
It's really fun.
And it happened in Target in South
Portland, Maine, right after my 50th
birthday. It was February, it was
snowing, and in Maine, probably like
here, it snows and they give you these
towels at Target to wipe out the snow
out of the shopping carts that come in
from the parking lot. This particular
day I got there, and there were all the
shopping carts were wet, but there were
no towels. But there was this little
millennial girl at the door, she was the
Target greeter that day.
Her name was Amanda, and she was just
getting through her 3-hour grueling
shift at Target.
Uh and I said, "Amanda, where are those
towels? These shopping carts are wet."
She goes, "Ah, they're still wet from
last night."
I said, "It's 2:00 in the afternoon."
She goes, "I know, it's almost time for
my break."
"Well, how am I supposed to shop? These
are wet." She said, "Well, you can just
take it in the bathroom and wipe it out
with a paper towel, duh."
And I thought, you know, my 30-year-old
self would have gone in the bathroom and
wiped it out with a paper towel. My
40-year-old self would have called
Amanda's manager over, and we would have
had a discussion about customer service
and how bad Amanda sucked at it.
But my 50-year-old self just took my
shopping cart directly to the first
clothing section that I came to.
And I just lined it with little boys'
T-shirts and soaked up all the water in
there.
AND THEN I SHOPPED FOR AN HOUR AND A
HALF, AND THEN I GOT TO THE checkout
line, and I paid for the things that I
wanted. And I got down to those shirts,
I said, "You know what? I have decided I
don't want these, they're wet."
Maybe Amanda can wipe them out on her
little break.
I'm 50.
I DON'T CARE.
I HAD ALL THE JOBS WORKING BACK IN THE
HOOD, MAN. When I was young, I worked in
retail. Anybody ever work retail before?
That was about the right reaction.
I WORKED AT TARGET, MAN. NOTHING AGAINST
TARGET. It was cool, but they want to
cross-train you in every department, so
you were useful at Target, okay? So, I
wasn't just a cashier, I was in guest
services, I was a cart attendant, I was
in the gardening center for like a day.
That was
cuz I don't know nothing about
gardening. So, I was just lying to
people all day long.
This old lady come up to me with this
plant, like, "How do you take care of
this plant?" Water it.
And if it starts to die, water it less.
There's a middle ground where you
operate in there somewhere.
Electronics was the department I got
fired in though, man. I know less about
electronics than I do about gardening.
Guy came up to me with a camera, "Hey,
how you work this camera?"
WATER IT.
AND IF IT starts to die, water it less.
Saw a lady recently crying in the middle
of the aisle at Target, just in the
middle of the ugly crying, hard crying,
okay? And I was like, "Oh, no, I should
do something." So, I'm in Target, I get
myself ready. She's crying so hard. I go
right up to her, and I'm like, "Excuse
me, ma'am, uh I think you mean to be in
Walmart right now. So."
Nailed that interaction. Yeah.
HOW ABOUT HOW ABOUT DON'T CRY IN TARGET,
KAREN, OKAY? I'm not paying an extra 15
cents for macaroni and cheese to see you
cry.
Target is for champions, okay?
Ridiculous.
Oh gosh. Well, people are curious.
You're a comedian, what do you do with
your free time? Here's what I did today.
I put on a red polo shirt, pair of khaki
pants, I went down to Target, and I
messed with people.
THAT'S FUN.
OH, AND THE FIRST THING YOU DISCOVER,
women love Target.
So much you have your own special name
for it. What do you call it, ladies?
Target.
You walk in there, "Hello, Target."
You don't go to J.C. Penney wall.
No.
Target is more special.
TARGET IS SO SPECIAL, YOU DON'T EVEN SEE
A mom yell at her child there. It's
sacred grounds.
Not the case at Walmart.
Different story at Walmart. It's more
exciting there.
You're liable to see somebody beating
the crap out of their child
in every aisle.
If you don't BELIEVE ME, PERK UP YOUR
ears next time. HERE'S WHAT YOU'LL GET.
"YOU LITTLE DEADBEAT. IF YOUR DADDY
WASN'T SUCH A LOSER, and actually MADE
SOME MONEY, WE'D BE SHOPPING AT TARGET."
NOW, I don't want to start sounding like
I'm an elitist. I shop at them all.
Everybody's got a store they make fun
of.
People at Macy's make fun of the people
at Target. The Target people make fun of
the people at Walmart. The people at
Walmart make fun of the people at the
dollar store.
And that's where it ends.
Right? Cuz the people at the dollar
store, they we got no place to make fun
of.
Hey, let's go to Goodwill, our stuff's
new.
Right?
Now, they say that imitation is the most
sincere form of flattery.
Well, if that's the case,
then why has every fight I've ever had
with my husband started with the phrase,
"Here, I'll be you."
Yeah, this will be good. No, I'm going
to be you. Here, I'll do it. I got it.
"Oh, my wife is so mean.
She makes me take out the garbage all by
myself."
Yeah.
Yeah. And then of course, he starts in,
like, "TARGET, TARGET, SHOP at Target.
Spend all OUR MONEY AT TARGET. OREOS,
OREOS, TARGET, TARGET, TARGET."
I'm like, I get the Oreos, but why you
got to bring Target into this?
Not cool, dude.
Men, they don't get it. They don't get
why we love Target. It's like, "Babe, I
know when we got married, I said that
you made all my dreams come true,
but it's actually Target."
Target's slogan should be, "Come for
deodorant, leave with everything else."
Yeah.
I spent less than $20 at Target one
time.
Yeah, thank you. I know.
It was incredible. Um
I took a picture of my receipt, texted
it to my husband. It's the only thing
framed on his desk at work.
He basically threw a parade in my honor.
You guys, he still brags about it to his
friends. Like, you got to keep her, man,
she's a keeper.
Anytime we have a fight, I'm like,
"Yeah, but that one time I didn't I only
spent $20 at Target."
So, we're walking towards Target, she
finally looks up from her phone, and she
goes, "Hey, Mom, what does this symbol
FOR TARGET MEAN?"
AGAIN, INTELLIGENT CROWD, intelligent
crowd.
"What does the symbol for Target mean?"
I just looked at her and go, "It means
COMMUNITY COLLEGE, HONEY."
SHE WENT, "DOES IT REALLY?" I WAS LIKE,
"YES."
I'M SO SAVING on this one. I am.
She really does, she hates that joke.
She does, she gets so annoyed. She's
like, "I mean, it's just a circle within
a circle." So, IT'S A TARGET.
IT'S A LOT. IT'S A LOT TO KEEP UP WITH
MILLENNIALS. I'm trying really hard.
I had multiple awkward experiences at
the grocery store, too. The sec- the
second awkward thing that happened at
the grocery store, I got yelled at by
the grocery cart corral guy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the grocery cart
corral guy, that's the person that that
gets all the carts that are out in the
in the like the parking lot, like at a
Target or Walmart grocery, and then just
brings the cart to the entryway. I
didn't know they could yell at you. They
can yell at you.
And it was all a miscommunication cuz I
had put my groceries in in my car, and
then when I when I put my car away, uh I
when I'm at those kind of places, I like
to find a corral that's really far away,
and I like to get some speed going, and
I like to kind of get a run in and then
let it go and watch it fly and bang
around in the corral. Like, that's a
really exciting Tuesday for me when I
get to do that.
So, I did I found my corral, I executed
the maneuver perfectly, but apparently
there had been the corral guy was
standing at a corral that was right next
to my car,
uh and he just thought he was waiting
for me patiently to put my groceries
away cuz he assumed I would just hand
him my cart like a normal human being.
But instead, he saw me just go, "Nope."
And just push it like a mile away.
And then like right when I let go, like
I realized something went wrong cuz he
was like, "For real?" And I like I like
looked over and I like was like,
And I I knew I could still solve the
problem cuz like like a normal person
would just run, grab the cart, bring it
back to him, and be like, "Oh, I'm
sorry. That was rude. I didn't see you."
But I just panicked and was like, "Oh,
no." And just got my car and drove away.
So, I'm pretty sure that guy hates me.
He might have been the one that put ice
on my driveway.
I am not in a gang. Don't let the Target
outfit fool you.
Yes, it is Target. It's Italian. Um
Massimo, I believe is the designer's
name.
Massimo Maroni. Um
Massimo is an Italian word meaning under
$20.
I uh